Everyone who hurt you is dead
I'll cover you with a blanket, sit you on the windowsill
I'll crawl under the sweater, into the very heart
You're cold St. Petersburg, but one can warm up in you
Each remained as a scar on the wrist
I will kill all those who dared to touch you
Crumpled sheets; they turned off the lights
We're made for each other, a defective duet
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…
I would like to become your blanket
So you sleep with me at night and don't get cold
To warm you with what's left of me
Just so you don't fall ill, just so you smile in the morning
I would like to live with you in one body
Ignoring the neighbors who bang on the radiators
By day or by night — it doesn't matter
I'm so happy with you in this big high-rise
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…
Ooh
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…